export default[
    {
        question:"1.Which of the following ancient Tamil Kingdoms came to be known from Sangam Literature?",
        options : [ "Chola","Chera","Pandya","All of the above"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"2.Where was the first Tamil Sangam held__?",
        options : [ "Madurai","Kapatpuram","Kaveripattnam","Kural"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"3.Which of the following book is considered as the ‘Odyssus of Tamil poetry’?",
        options : [ "Tirukkural","Manimekalai","Silappadikarma","Jivaka Chintaman"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"4.Which of the following was the capital of Chola dynasty?",
        options : [ "Madurai","Karur","Uraiyaur","Kaveripattnam"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:"5.The Pattini cult was established by which Sangam ruler?",
        options : [ "Nedunjeral Adan, the Chera ruler","Senguttuvan, the Chera rule","Karikala, the Chola ruler","Nedujeliyan, the Pandyan ruler"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"6.Which among the following is a Tamil grammatical treatise ?",
        options : [ "Pattupattu","Ettutogai","Silappadikaram","Tolkappiam"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"7.“Kuyil Pattu” is a famous work ascribed to which among the following Tamil Poets?",
        options : [ "Bharathidasan","Avvaiyar","Anandabharati Aiyangar","Subramanya Bharathi"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"8.Which among the following National Parks / Wild Life sanctuaries of Tamil Nadu is called as Top Slip?",
        options : [ "Aanamalai National Park","Mudumalai Wildlife Sanctuary","Guindy National Park"," Palani Hills National Park"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"9.Jayamkondam in Tamil Nadu is famous for which among the following minerals?",
        options : [ "Bauxite","Lignite","Calcite","Magnesite"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"10.Which among the following sites near Pondicherry gives best support to the view on an ancient trade between Rome and the ancient Tamil country of India?",
        options : [ "Villianur","Suttukeni","Arikamedu","Andiarpalayam"],
        answer:2
    },
]


